Rochester, New York and Vicinity Labor Council, AFL-CIO Records 6239
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Rochester, New York and Vicinity Labor Council, AFL-CIO Records
1956-2007
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Garlock, Jonathan
Anderson, Marilyn
Rochester and Vicinity Labor Council, AFL-CIO
6239
13 cubic feet
13 linear ft.
Records.
This collection consists of manuscript sheets, pamphlets, constitutions, unbound newspapers, computer disks, photographs and some memorabilia.
6194428
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, May 02, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 25, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6239 AV: Rochester, New York and Vicinity Labor Council, AFL-CIO Audio-Visual Materials 6239 MB: Rochester, New York and Vicinity Labor Council, AFL-CIO Memorabilia 6239 P: Rochester, New York and Vicinity Labor Council, AFL-CIO Photographs
Rochester and Vicinity Labor Council
6194428
- Colombo Scholarship. Files. 1975-2000. (Box 1)
  - Donations - Colombo Fund (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - James S. Colombo Fund 1980-81, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Scholarship Selection Committee J.S. Colombo, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Colombo Scholarship Dinner, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - James S. Colombo Scholarship Financial Reports and Receipts Bank (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - James S. Colombo - Award Dinner Reservation Acknowledgements (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Addresses - For Invitations Scholarship Dinner (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Columbo Scholarship (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Colombo Fund (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 1999-2000 Colombo Scholarship (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - J.S.C. Scholarship Recipient @ $750.00, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - JSC Scholarship, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Colombo Scholarship - Recipients 4 @ $500.00, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Colombo Scholarship Recipients @ 1000, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Colombo Scholarship Recipients 2 @ 1000, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Colombo Scholarship Recipients - 2@1000, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Colombo Scholarship Recipients - 2@1000, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Colombo Scholarship - Recipients 2@1000, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Colombo Scholarship Recipients - 2@500.00, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Colombo Scholarship Fund - 2@1000 Recipients, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Colombo Scholarship Recipients - 2@1000, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Colombo Scholarship Recipients - 3@1000, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Colombo Scholarship Recipients - 2@1000, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Colombo Scholarship Recipients - 2@1500, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Colombo Scholarship Recipients - 3@1000, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Colombo Scholarship Recipients - 3@1000, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Colombo Scholarship Recipients - 5@1000, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Financial Statements (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Minutes of Meetings (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Colombo Scholarships (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Council Meetings. Minutes and Materials. 1970-1990. (Box 2)
  - Board Meetings 1970 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 1975 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 1976 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 1977 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 1978 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 1979 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 1980 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 1981 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 1982 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 1983 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 1985 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 1986 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 1987 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 1988 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Jan'89 Eboard/Council (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Feb'89 Eboard/Council (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Mar'89 Eboard/Council (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Apr'89 Eboard/Council (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - May'89 Eboard/Council, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - June'89 Eboard/Council, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - July'89 Eboard/Council, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Aug'89 Eboard/Council, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Sep'89 Eboard/Council (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Oct'89 Eboard/Council, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Nov'89 Eboard/Council, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Dec'89 Eboard/Council, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - 1989 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Jan'90 Eboard/Council, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Feb'90 Eboard/Council (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Mar'90 Eboard/Council (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Apr'90 Eboard/Council (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - May'90 Eboard/Council (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - June'90 Eboard/Council (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - July'90 Eboard/Council (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Aug'90 Eboard/Council (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Sep'90 Eboard/Council (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Oct'90 Eboard/Council (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Nov'90 Eboard/Council (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Dec'90 Eboard/Council (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - 1990 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Council Meetings. Minutes and Materials. 1991-1995. (Box 3)
  - Council Meetings January 1991 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Council Meetings February 1991 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Council Meetings March 1991 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Council Meetings April 1991 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Council Meetings May 1991 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Council Meetings June 1991 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Council Meetings July 1991 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Council Meetings August 1991 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Council Meetings September 1991 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Council Meetings October 1991 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Council Meetings November 1991 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Council Meetings (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - 1991 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Council Meetings January 1992 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Council Meetings February 1992 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Council Meetings March 1992 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Council Meetings April 1992 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Council Meetings (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Council Meetings (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Council Meetings (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Council Meetings (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Council Meetings September 1992 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Council Meetings October 1992 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Council Meetings November 1992 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Council Meetings (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - 1992 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Council Meetings January 1993 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Council Meetings (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Council Meetings March 1993 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Council Meetings April 1993 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Council Meetings May 1993 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Council Meetings June 1993 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Council Meetings July 1993 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Council Meetings August 1993 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Council Meetings September 1993 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Council Meetings October 1993 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Council Meetings November 1993 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Council Meetings December 1993 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - 1993 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Council Meetings 1994 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - 1994 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - 1995 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Meeting Attendance Books. 1979-1995; Annual Reports. 1984-1996; Executive Board. Files. 1985-1989; Council. Correspondence. 1976-1988; Treasurer's Reports. 1983-1989; Fincance Committee. Minutes. 1997-1998. (Box 4)
  - Attendance Book 1977-1985 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Attendance Book 1979-1995 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Annual Reports, 1984-1999 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Financial Reports (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - E-Board: Appointments (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - E-Board: Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Documents to Save (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Council Correspondence 1980 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Council Correspondence 1981 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Council Correspondence 1982 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Council Correspondence 1983 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Council Correspondence 1984 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Council Correspondence 1985 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Council Correspondence 1986 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Council Correspondence 1987 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Council Correspondence 1988 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Misc. Correspondence 1994 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Misc. Correspondence 1995 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Misc. Corresp. '96, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Bruce (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Bruce-mail (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Council Correspondence Stationery (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Minutes 1997 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Minutes 1998 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Education Committee. Files. 1986-2007. (Box 5)
  - Executive Board Meeting (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - EO CTTE (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - TO Education CTTE (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 1996 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 1998 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 1999 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - 2000 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - 2001 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - 2002 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Minutes 2003 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - 2004 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - 2005 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - 2006 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Teaching Work - Jon Garlock (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Resumes-Upward Bound (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - WDTW (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Teachnet (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Doug Teachnet (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Grant Acct(Fleet Bank) (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - AFL-CIO(HRDI) Contract (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - J.F. Weoman Fund (Map/Guide) (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - J.F. Weoman Fund(Barlow,Goldman) (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - AGR Exhibit, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - NYSED - Exhibit, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - NYSED - Exhibit/Coloring Book, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - NYSED - Coloring Book, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - NYSED - Expand Exhibit, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Labor History Module (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Executive Board (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Educom -2000 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Contracts with MCC (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - STW-Western Monroe (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - STW (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Why Work (STW) (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - DDE, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - DDE 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - REAC (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - DDE 98/03 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - REAC (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - School to Work (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - DDE 97/98 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Service to Inst. (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - STW 96-03 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - STW-Eastern Monroe 98-06 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Labor Council Letterhead (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Locals. Files. A-P. (Box 6)
  - ACTWU (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - ACTWU@ Kleenbrite, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - AFM 66, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - AFSCME Council 66 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Teamsters 18 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - AFSCME (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - AFSCME 1635 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - AFSCME 2419 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - AFSCME 3357 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - APWU (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - ATU 282: RTS Contract (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - ATU 1610 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Baker 116 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Carpenters 85 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - CSEA (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - CSEA State Workers, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - CSEA Golf (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Ron/CWA (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - CWA Letters, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - MTG/CWA, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - CWA 1170 @ Henrietta September 30, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - CWA 1170 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - GCIU 36 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - GCIU 38 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Glaziers, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Here and Now 466 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - IAFF 1071 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - IAFF 1636 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - IAM (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - IATSE B-90 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - IATSE 253/Greyhound, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Scope and Contents
    March 9. 1990
  - I.A.M. Local 93 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - IAM 1439IAM 2312 Strike 4/94 Teamsters 118 Strike (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - International Jewelry Wkrs. Local 39 GCIU (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - IUE District 3 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - IUE 342 '91 CVC Products (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - IUE 381 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    June 9, 1989
  - IUPA (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Marble and Tile Local 75 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Millwrights 1163 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Nabet 22 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - NALC 210 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - National Writers Union (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Newspaper Guild 17 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Newspaper Guild @ Gannett September 8, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - NYSUT (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - PEF (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Public Employees Federation (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - PEF 283 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - PEF 259 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    November 2, 1989
  - PEF 283 @RPC (Box 6, Folder 52)
    April 6, 1990
  - PEF Layoffs, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - PEF (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - PEF Division Local 307 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Physicians and Dentists - Fed of. (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Plumbers 13 @ Bell, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    June 23, 1989
  - Plumbers 13 (Box 6, Folder 58)
- Locals. Files. R-U. (Box 7)
  - RWDSU (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Roofers 22 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - RSBEA '96, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Seafarers (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Local 1199 NUHHCE/SSEIU (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - SEIU 200C Nat'l (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - SEIU 222 - WROTB COMTRACT (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - VOA - 1199 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    July 1990
  - 1199 VOA '92, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - SEIU 721, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - SEIU 721 '91 Strike, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - SEIU (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Serv. Empl. Intern'l Union Local 222 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Teamsters (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Teamsters 118 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Teamsters 118, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    November 5, 1989
  - Teamsters 791: Channel 13 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Typographers (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - UNITE (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - UAW 2320 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - UAW (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - UFCW (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - United Marine Division (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - UMW: Pittston Strike (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - UMW @ Pittston: 1989 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - UMW Food shipment 11/89, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - United Paperworkers (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - UUP (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - USWA 1755 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - USWA 1755, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    May 1990
  - USWA 4146: Roehlen Engraving (1991) (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - United Steelworkers of Amer. Local #4457 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - USWA 4680 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - USWA 4680 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - United Steelworkers Local #5334 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - United Steelworkers Local #1497 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - UTU 1472 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- President. Files. 1984-1996. (Box 8)
  - President's Report: 1985 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - President's Report: 1986 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - President's Report: 1987 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - President's Report: 1988 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - President's Report: 1989 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Speeches (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - January (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - February (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - April (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - May (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - July (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - August (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - September (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - October (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - November (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - December (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - January (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - February (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - March (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - April '96 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - May (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - June (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - July '96 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - August (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - September (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - October (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - November (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - December (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Companys. Files.; Labor Day Parade. Files. 1986-2006. (Box 9)
  - Austin Cablevision Strike 1992 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Bastian Brothers (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Blue Cross/Blue Shield (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Blue Cross Rate Hearing - November 20, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Coors Boycott: 1987 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Daily News Strike: 1990 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Dresser-Rand/IUE 313, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Eastern Airlines (IAM) 1989 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Gannett Unions '93, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Greyhound: 1990 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Greyhound '91, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - IAM @ Eastern Air: 1989 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Kleen Brite 1991 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - K-Mart Boycott (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Kodak Organizing (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Van Heusen 3/21/92 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Little Theatre: IATSE 253 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - MT Bank - April 1990 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Nestle Boycott (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Ravenswood '92 - Steelworkers (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Building Trades/RG&E: 1990 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - RG&E Rate-Hike Hearing (Box 9, Folder 22)
    November 20, 1989
  - Walmart (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Wegman's Blog Trades (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Wegman's 1995 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - 1986 LDP (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Parade: 1986 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Parade Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - 1987 LDP (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Parade: 1987 (Misc.) (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Parade: 1987 (Guests) (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Parade: 1987 (Participation) (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Parade: 1988 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Parade '89 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Parade 1990 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Labor Day Parade 1991 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Seabreeze/ '92 Parade, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Parade '93, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Parade '94, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Parade '95, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Parade '96, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Labor Day Parade, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    September 7, 1998
  - MD Parade (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - 1997 Labor Day Parade (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - 1998 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - LDP Postering 1999 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - 2002 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - 2003 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - LDP 2004 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - LDP 05 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - 2006 LDP (Box 9, Folder 51)
- Subject Files. A-C.. (Box 10)
  - AFL-CIO Consultation (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - AFL-CIO Economics ED (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Nat'l AFL-CIO Foreign Policy (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Nat'l AFL-CIO: Central Bodies (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Nat'l AFL-CIO: Misc. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Constitution AFL-CIO (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - NYS AFL-CIO: Misc. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - AFL-CIO By-Laws (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - AFL-CIO, Rochester, Charity Fund (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - AIDS (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Action! Motown, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Affiliates (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - 1988 Affil. Survey (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Affirmative Action (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Anti-Scab Bill: 1990 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Anti-Scab (1991) (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - AGR Photo Proj. (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Attorneys (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Frank Barbaro Fundraiser (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Benson, Norb. (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Bertolone, James (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Bill of Rights (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - 1991 Budget (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Budget 1993 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Workmen (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - COPE (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - COPE 1997 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Misc. COPE items 1987-1991 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - COPE Committee (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - COPE (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Calendar 1984 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Calendar 1993 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Calendar 1994 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Campaign for New Priorities (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Chavez - April 4, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Clippings (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Committees (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Computing (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Constitution (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Contract Campaign Wkshp, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Cornell Internship (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Credentials '95, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Cunningham, Songbook (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Cuomo: Pre-1989 (Box 10, Folder 44)
- Subject Files. D-J.. (Box 11)
  - Delegate List (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - "Democracy at Work" June 11 COPE Conference (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Democratic Committee, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    February 28, 1997
  - Desert March, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    January 15, 1992
  - Dinner, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Directory Data (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Directory (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - 1994 Directory (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Directory of Local Unions 1990-1996 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Displaced Wrkrs 88-89, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Doublebreasting (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Drug Testing (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Drug Testing Seminar, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    December 13, 1989
  - EAPS - Misc. (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Rochester and Vicinity Labor Council - Education Committee (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Endorsement Letters '96, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Film Series (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Film Series '95 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Fink, Tom (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Flores, Rick - Labor Cartoon Service (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Folklore Productions (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Fraser Dinner (Box 11, Folder 22)
    October 30
  - Free Trade -1991 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Free Trade "Fast Track" 1991 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Gaby, Alex (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Garlock, Schedule 1994 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Chris Recep, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    January 31
  - Genesee Valley Foodbank (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Healthcare '92 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Healthcare 1993 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Healthcare '94, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Healthcare (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Managed Care '93, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Preferred Care (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Health Care Rally, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    October 3, 1990
  - June 6 Healthcare Rally (1991) (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - History (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - ILCA (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Industrial Management Council (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Israel Bonds CTTE (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Jobs Bill '93, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Job Description (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Coordinator Job Description (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - JDA (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Job Training Partnership Act (JTPA) (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - JWJ Conference (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - "Jobs/Justice" Rally (Box 11, Folder 47)
- Subject Files. L-R.. (Box 12)
  - Labor Archives 1992 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Labor Councils (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Labor Day Solidarity III, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Labor Day, Intervention 1994 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Labor Information Seminar (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Labor News (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Labor/Religion Coalition (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Labor to Labor Phone Bank (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Labor's New Anthem (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Latin American Del., 1996 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Metro Act (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Metro Justice (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Mobilizer Alert (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Monroe County: Legislature (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - County Courts '92, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - County Elections 1991 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - County Workers '94, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Michael Moore (Roger & Me) (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Nafta 1993 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - NAFTA '95, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - New Affiliate Campaign, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - 1199 Organizing (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Org. Comm. (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Personnel Comm., 1998 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Personnel Comm. (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Pettengill Scholarship (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Picnic 1991 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - PLNG. Mtg., 1998 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Bruce Popper (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Prevailing Wage (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Private Industry Council (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Privatization '92, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Program Comm. (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Program Committee (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Republican Party - Monroe Co. (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Resistance Survey (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Right to Work (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - ROCOSH (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Roch Area Religion & Labor Co. (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Rochester Coalition on Economic Priorities (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - City Council: Rochester (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Rochester City (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Rochester Labor CTTE on Central America (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Rochester Labor History Map/Guide (Box 12, Folder 44)
- Subject Files. S-W.. (Box 13)
  - Sister Cities (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Solidarity Day '91, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Sweatshops (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Union Label Service Trades 1979 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Union Label Surveys - Completed (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Union Label Convention 1981 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Union Label Directory: 1991 Working File (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Union Label (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Union Label (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Union Label and Service Trades Dept. (Box 13, Folder 10)